Guide to the Faculty Committee on Athletics, Yale University, Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Faculty Committee on Athletics, Yale University, records
1977-1998
RU 984
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
1.5
(2 boxes)
The records consist of proceedings of the Yale Faculty Committee on Athletics.
Yale University. Faculty Committee on Athletics
General note
Forms part of Yale Record Group 38-A (YRG 38-A), Records documenting administration of Yale athletic and physical education programs.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
The records were transferred from the Department of Athletics, Yale University, 2005.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the materials is restricted. See Collection Contents for details.
Arrangement
The records are arranged chronologically.
Biographical / Historical
The Faculty Committee on Athletics is appointed annually by the Yale president. It serves in an advisory capacity to the director of athletics and to the president. The committee meets monthly to discuss issues affecting athletes and athletics at Yale.
Scope and Contents
The records consist of proceedings of the Yale Faculty Committee on Athletics.
Athletics; College sports; Yale University -- Sports; Yale University. Dept. of Athletics; Yale University. Faculty Committee on Athletics
- Proceedings of the Faculty Committee on Athletics, 1977-1998; Accession 2006-A-004
  Conditions Governing Access
  Restricted until January 2033
  - 1977-1978 (Box 1)
  - 1978-1979 (Box 1)
  - 1979-1980 (Box 1)
  - 1980-1981 (Box 1)
  - 1981-1982 (Box 1)
  - 1982-1983 (Box 1)
  - 1983-1984 (Box 1)
  - 1984-1985 (Box 1)
  - 1985-1986 (Box 1)
  - 1986-1987 (Box 1)
  - 1987-1990 (Box 1)
  - 1990-1992 (Box 1)
  - 1992-1994 (Box 1)
  - 1994-1998 (Box 2)
  - 1995-1998 (Box 2)